Multiple choice is a choice-based question
type with single choice selection.
cue-2
To add a multiple choice question,
cue-3
click the Insert Content icon
cue-4
and select Multiple Choice Question.
cue-5
Make sure to edit the multiple choice
title.
cue-6
This is for your reference and will be
very important to the readability of our
cue-7
data analysis.
cue-8
Students will not see the question title.
cue-9
Remember to click Save after you finish
your changes to the title.
cue-10
Adding learning objectives to your
question follows the same process as
cue-11
adding learning objectives to a page.
cue-12
In accordance with learning engineering
principles and to enable meaningful data
cue-13
analysis, all questions should have at
least one associated learning objective or
cue-14
sub-objective.
cue-15
To begin authoring your question, in the
question text box, enter the text of the
cue-16
question or question stem.
cue-17
This will be presented to students as a
question they need to respond to.
cue-18
For example, let's enter, "Which planet in
the solar system is closest to the Sun?"
cue-19
The same formatting and content inserting
options available in the paragraph blocks
cue-20
are available for the question stem.
cue-21
Next, add the answer choices.
cue-22
These are the answer options your learners
can select from.
cue-23
You can add as many choices as needed.
cue-24
Here, I will add three answer choices as
an example.
cue-25
To add another answer choice, click Add
Choice below the existing choices.
cue-26
To delete a particular answer choice,
click the X's to the right of the answer
cue-27
choice.
cue-28
You have two options for the order in
which students will see the answer
cue-29
choices. If answer choices are shuffled,
cue-30
students will see them in a randomly
determined order.
cue-31
If answer choices are not shuffled,
cue-32
students will see them in the order they
appear in authoring.
cue-33
To select your desired option,
cue-34
click the three dots menu on the far right
above the question stem.
cue-35
Check or uncheck the Shuffle Answer
Choices checkbox.
cue-36
To reorder the answer choices, click the
drag handle to the left of an answer
cue-37
choice and drag it into the desired
position.
cue-38
To set which answer choice will be marked
as correct,
cue-39
go to the Answer Key tab.
cue-40
Simply select the radio button next to a
correct answer.